firecams.com 2015-12-19

# Privacy Policy at FireCams | FireCams.com - Live Cam Sex

('We') [Bulova Invest Ltd](http://www.firecams.com/) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.   
This policy (together with our terms and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

We are the data controller for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the 'Act').

## What information do we collect about you?

We may collect and process the following information about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site [firecams.com](http://www.firecams.com/) (the 'Site') (including your personal details, contact details, mobile phone number and other profile information you submit when you create a membership profile). We may also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions. 
  * Information from your web-based email accounts (including your profile picture and other publicly visible information) if you agree to add the Site's email address to the contact lists stored at your email provider's website.
  * Your location according to the IP address assigned to your PC by your Internet Service Provider.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through the Site, including any information we require to provide any products or services that you order from us through the Site. 
  * Website usage information is also collected using cookies (see below under 'Cookies').

## How will we use the information about you?

We use the information we hold about you in the following ways:

  * To administer your user account with us (including notifying you of any compatible matches, tips, announcements, updates, special offers or services, should you consent to this).
  * To help us improve the structure, layout and usability of the Site.
  * To allow you to participate in any interactive features of the Site(including the features that require the mobile phone number).
  * To help personalise your repeat visits to the Site.
  * To notify you of any compatible matches or any matches who are near your location.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes (see below under 'Marketing by us and third parties' for more information). Such information may be sent to you by email or by SMS (if you provided your mobile phone number).
  * To answer any questions you may raise or respond to any comments you may send to us.
  * To notify you about changes to our service or the functionality of the Site.
  * To carry out market analysis and research.
  * To ensure that you are complying with the  Terms and conditions of use and to comply with our statutory and regulatory obligations. 

## What information do we collect about others?

  * Some features of the Site allow you to share your Site experience with people you know (your Contacts), or to invite them to join the Site. When given the option to do so you can choose to upload your Contacts information; we will request their name and email address.
  * If you give us your password to upload these Contacts through a web based email provider we shall not store your password after you have uploaded your Contact's addresses.

## How do we use information about contacts?

  * If you choose to upload your Contact's name and email address you are allowing us to send an email invitation on your behalf, inviting your Contact to join the Site.
  * We will store your Contact's name and email address solely for the purposes of inviting them to join our Site and for associating your Contact with you and other people they may know.
  * If your Contact does not want us to store their email address which you uploaded to our Site, they can ask us to remove it by contacting us at [support@firecams.com](mailto:support@firecams.com). 
  * We will not store your Contacts information after invitations (up to a maximum of 3) have been sent. Your Contacts will then only receive future emails from us if they choose to accept the invitation and join our Site, or if you use any of our tools to share experiences with your Contacts and you input their email address for us to use again.

## Disclosure of your information

We will only use or disclose your personal information in accordance with the purposes for which it was originally collected unless you have otherwise consented, or when required or permitted by law. We will keep your personal information only for so long as is required to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected or as required by law. Except as explained in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise consented to by you, we do not disclose any personal information to third parties. The following are the limited instances where we may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * When this information must be shared to provide a product or service you have requested.
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on our behalf to provide a product or service to you.
  * To investigate and/or enforce violations of our Terms and Conditions of Use and/or this Privacy Policy, or to protect our interests in our operation and our legal rights and protections.
  * To investigate potentially fraudulent or questionable activities.
  * When required or permitted by law. [FireCams](http://www.firecams.com/) (including our affiliates, advertisers and content providers) independently reserves the right to fully cooperate with requests from any recognized law enforcement authority, and to court orders, requesting or directing [FireCams](http://www.firecams.com/) (including our affiliates, advertisers and content providers) to disclose the identity or other information regarding any person who is using or has used the Site or the Service or has obtained any Content available through or in association with the Site. By accepting this Privacy Policy and using the Site and/or the Service, you waive and hold harmless [FireCams](http://www.firecams.com/), our affiliates, content providers, and the operators of the Site from any and all claims resulting from any and all actions taken by any of the foregoing during, or as a result of any law enforcement authority's investigations or inquiries. 
  * In the course of a sale or potential sale, reorganization, consolidation, merger or amalgamation of our business. In order to ensure a smooth transition of the Service in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of all or substantially all of its assets or the sale of an individual website owned by [Bulova Invest Ltd](http://www.firecams.com/), [Bulova Invest Ltd](http://www.firecams.com/) may transfer your personally identifiable information to a third party as a part of such merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale. In the event the transaction proceeds, we will require that the receiving party agree that they will be similarly bound by the provisions of this Privacy Policy and that they will only use and disclose your personal information as we are similarly entitled under this Privacy Policy. In the event the sale does not proceed, we will require the potential purchaser to not use or disclose your personal information in any manner whatsoever and to completely erase the same. 

Where such disclosure is described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not protect information you post to any online profile, chat room, or any other forum accessible to other Users or other sites within [Bulova Invest Ltd](http://www.firecams.com/). 

## Marketing and other uses of your non-personal data by us and by third parties

We may share non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may share it with our own companies or other third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising to you, or to help us prepare or share aggregate business and marketing reports.

We would like to send you information about goods and services offered by us and selected third parties that we think may be of interest to you. For that, the email address or mobile phone number you have provided can be used. To unsubscribe or change your email options go to the “My Account” area, choose “Email Settings” section and edit the notifications preferences. 

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes please tick the appropriate boxes situated in the 'my account' area of the Site.

## Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve the Site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:

  * To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise the Site according to your individual interests.
  * To speed up your searches.
  * To recognise you when you return to the Site.

For further information about cookies visit:[http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above website tells you how to do that. However, in a few cases some of the features on our Site may not function as a result. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to the Site.

## Where we store your personal data

The personal data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a location outside the European Economic Area ('EEA'). It may also be processed by staff located outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers (for example, staff who are involved in providing services that you order from us, processing your payment details or providing support services for the Site). By submitting your personal data to us through the Site, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password or user ID code which enables you to access certain parts of the Site, you are responsible for keeping the password or user ID code confidential. We ask you not to share a password or user ID code with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Athough we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Other Websites

The Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Access to information and correction

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us at [support@firecams.com](mailto:support@firecams.com). Please note that we may make a small charge for this service. 

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You can ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate at any time by e-mailing us at [support@firecams.com](mailto:support@firecams.com). 

## Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will post any changes to it on this page. We encourage you to regularly review our privacy policy to make sure you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we may share it with other parties

## Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy policy then please contact us at [FireCams](http://www.firecams.com/) or contact us through e-mail: [ support@firecams.com](mailto:support@firecams.com)

Tel: 1 8008685182
